Guide to the UE Publications Collection, 1936-1990s UE.8.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- The Proud Record of an American Union, Third Edition, March 1952 (Box 4, Folder 265)
- Unfair Regarding Blacks and Fair Employment Practices Commission, March 1952 (Box 4, Folder 265)
- The Road to Full Employment Regarding Foreign Policy and Political Action, March 1952 (Box 4, Folder 266)
- The Old Shell Game Regarding Profits and Wages, March 1952 (Box 4, Folder 266)
- What Price Double Standard? Regarding Women, March 1952 (Box 4, Folder 266)
- They Want to Deport Citizens Regarding Lustig Case, March 1952 (Box 4, Folder 266)
- IUE Founder Blasts IUE Dictatorship, April 1952 (Box 4, Folder 266)
- The Real Humphrey Regarding Red-baiting and Political Action, April 1952 (Box 4, Folder 267)
- Fighting for the People Regarding Emspak-Quinn Case and Red-baiting, April 1952 (Box 4, Folder 267)
- Don't Buy Westinghouse Regarding Local 443 Trenton Westinghouse Strikes, April 1952 (Box 4, Folder 267)
- They All Want Them Regarding Skilled Workers, April 1952 (Box 4, Folder 267)
- Discrimination Hurts Everybody Regarding Women, Blacks, Skilled and Wages, May 1952 (Box 4, Folder 267)
- Corporation Profits Skyrocket Regarding Profits and Wages, May 1952 (Box 4, Folder 267)
- Taxes Take Bigger Bites Regarding Negotiations and Political Action, May 1952 (Box 4, Folder 268)
- Profits Up, Up, Up Regarding Profits, Negotiations and Political Action, May 1952 (Box 4, Folder 268)
- Dollar Value Dwindles Regarding Negotiations and Political Action, May 1952 (Box 4, Folder 268)
- BLS Figures Cheat Us Regarding Wages, May 1952 (Box 4, Folder 268)
- The Big Lie Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, May 1952 (Box 4, Folder 268)
- GE Knows It, Do You? Regarding General Electric and Organization, May 1952 (Box 4, Folder 269)
- Liberty in Trouble Regarding Red-baiting, May 1952 (Box 4, Folder 269)
- The Real Humphrey Regarding Political Action and Red-baiting, May 1952 (Box 4, Folder 269)
- UE Fights for FEPC, May 1952 (Box 4, Folder 270)
- Stop Thief! Regarding Runaway Shops, June 1952 (Box 4, Folder 271)
- Smith Bill Danger to All Unions, July 1952 (Box 4, Folder 271)
- The Ludlow Story Regarding General Electric and Runaway Shops, July 1952 (Box 4, Folder 271)
- What is A Mugwump Regarding Red-baiting, July 1952 (Box 4, Folder 271)
- The Rights We Live By Regarding Political Action, July 1952 (Box 4, Folder 271)
- Operation Intimidation Regarding Red-baiting, July 1952 (Box 4, Folder 272)
- In Defense of Labor Regarding Political Action and Red-baiting, July 1952 (Box 4, Folder 273)
- In Defense of Labor Regarding Political Action, July 1952 (Box 4, Folder 274)
- Our Republican Platform Regarding Political Action, August 1952 (Box 4, Folder 275)
- The Rights We Live By Regarding Political Action, August 1952 (Box 4, Folder 275)
- The Proud Record of an American Union, Fourth Edition, August 1952 (Box 4, Folder 275)
- Sing Regarding 1952 UE Convention, September 1952 (Box 4, Folder 276)
- Fighting for the People Regarding Emspak-Quinn Case Regarding Red-baiting, September 1952 (Box 4, Folder 276)
- 81,000 Workers Choose UE Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, September 1952 (Box 4, Folder 276)
- Side by Side Regarding Blacks and Women, September 1952 (Box 4, Folder 277)
- Vote Regarding Political Action, September 1952 (Box 4, Folder 277)
- The Strength of UE Regarding UE Program, October 1952 (Box 4, Folder 277)
- UE Fights for Women Workers, November 1952 (Box 4, Folder 278)
- One Day Out of Four Regarding Taxation, November 1952 (Box 4, Folder 279)
- Who Does the Work Regarding Children's Books, December 1952 (Box 4, Folder 279)
- Just One Vote Regarding Political Action, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 279)
- Here's What a Republican Congress Did for You, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 280)
- W Tried Everything Regarding Westinghouse Nuttall Strikes, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 281)
- The Old Shell Game Regarding Profits and Wages, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 281)
- War Economy: Threat to Our Living Standards, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 281)
- A Call Regarding New York Skilled Workers Conference, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 281)
- Men's Business Too Regarding Women and Wages, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 281)
- Guess Regarding Profits and Wages, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 281)
- What Can I Do? Regarding Republican Politics, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 282)
- Meet the Candidates Regarding Adlai Stevenson, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 282)
- Speed-up, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 282)
- My Credo and My Promise Regarding Women's National Republican Club, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 282)
- Your Stake in a UE Harvester Victory, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 283)
- Delegates National Assembly for Peace, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 283)
- Bosses, Not Unions Threaten America, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 283)
- How Can You Help Ike, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 283)
- Yalta to Korea Regarding Foreign Policy and Republicans, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 284)
- Pity the Poor Boss Regarding Profits and Wages, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 284)
- Republican Policy of Liberation or Democratic Policy of Containment, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 284)
- Freedom's Case of Against Dean Acheson, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 284)
- Repeal the Smith Act, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 284)
- They Want to Take Away My Citizenship Regarding, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 284)
- Be a Fact--Carrying Citizen Regarding Womens National Republican Committee, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 285)
- The Proud Record of UE in Sylvania, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 285)
- Here is The Proof Regarding Red-baiting, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 285)
- Man Bites Dog Regarding Red-baiting, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 286)
- Special Bulletin on Fair Practices Work, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 287)
- Socialists Plans for Control of the USA Regarding Red-baiting, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 288)
- What We Need Regarding Negotiations, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 289)
- UE Fights for Women Workers, January 1953 (Box 4, Folder 290)
- The UE 1953 Collective Bargaining Program, March 16, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 291)
- The UE 1953 Collective Bargaining Program, March 16, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 292)
- What Are They Really After? Regarding Matles Case and Red-baiting, March 1953 (Box 4, Folder 293)
- Sample Contract, March 1953 (Box 4, Folder 294)
- Analysis of Goldwater Rhodes Bill, April 1953 (Box 4, Folder 295)
- Women Fight for a Better Life, April 1953 (Box 4, Folder 296)
- Together We Win! Regarding Women, April 1953 (Box 4, Folder 297)
- UE Women Speak Out, May 1953 (Box 4, Folder 297)
- The Roosevelt Spirit Regarding Franklin D. Roosevelt, May 1953 (Box 4, Folder 298)
- Tips on Reaching the Public Regarding League of Women Voters, June 1953 (Box 4, Folder 299)
- That Book Had More Value to the Cause Than Ten Regiments Regarding Bookclub, June 1953 (Box 4, Folder 299)
- You and Your New Job Regarding General Electric and Membership Drive, July 1953 (Box 4, Folder 299)
- What About Our Health? Regarding Sylvania and Women, July 1953 (Box 4, Folder 300)
- That Book Had More Value to the Cause Than Ten Regiments Regarding Book Club, August 1953 (Box 4, Folder 300)
- Catalogue of Publications, September 1953 (Box 4, Folder 301)
- Farmer-Labor Teamwork, November 1953 (Box 4, Folder 302)
- What is McCarthyism, November 1953 (Box 4, Folder 303)
- A Bill Regarding Red-baiting and Butler Bill, November 1953 (Box 4, Folder 304)
- The People Are Fighting Back Against McCarthyism, December 2, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 305)
- The People Are Fighting Back Against McCarthyism, December 2, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 306)
- 1953 Cartoon Calendar, December 1953 (Box 5, Folder 307)
- Matles to McCarthy Regarding Red-baiting, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 307)
- In Danger Regarding Red-baiting, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 307)
- We Win With UE, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 307)
- The Fight for the Complete Vindication of Bridges, Robertson and Schmidt Is Not Over Regarding Red-baiting, and International Longshore and Warehouse Union, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 308)
- People Fight Back Against McCarthyism, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 308)
- A Federal Judge Exposes a Foul Blow Regarding Red-baiting, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 308)
- The Financial Affairs of McCarthy Regarding Red-baiting, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 309)
- UE Wins for All Labor Regarding National Labor Relations Board and Red-baiting, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 309)
- You're a Liar Senator Regarding Red-baiting, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 309)
- Taft-Hartleyism Is: Depression Maker Regarding Red-baiting and Political Action, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 310)
- Telling the Town Through TV Regarding Publicity, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 310)
- An Appeal to Reason Regarding National Lawyers Guild and Red-baiting, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 310)
- Beware of Anti-Union Frauds Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 310)
- The People Vs. McCarthyism, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 311)
- Read It for Yourself Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 311)
- The Emspak Case, First Version Regarding Red-baiting, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 311)
- Emspak Case, Second Version Regarding Red-baiting, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 311)
- 1953 UE Calendar (Box 5, Folder 312)
- H-Bomb for American Labor Regarding Butler Bill, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 313)
- National Conference on Problems of Working Women, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 313)
- GE's Lawbreaking Record, January 1945 (Box 5, Folder 314)
- Unity Wins for Us Regarding Westinghouse Lester, and IUE and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, January 1945 (Box 5, Folder 314)
- You're a Liar, Senator Regarding Red-baiting, February 1954 (Box 5, Folder 314)
- Defended Regarding Walter-McCavan Act and Deportations, February 28, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 315)
- A Dose of His Own Medicine Regarding Red-baiting and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, March 1954 (Box 5, Folder 315)
- UE Shop Steward Guide, March 1954 (Box 5, Folder 316)
- We of UE Are in a Mighty Crusade Regarding Political Action and Red-baiting, April 1954 (Box 5, Folder 317)
- Facts to Combat Job Discrimination Regarding Women's Conference, May 15, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 317)
- Facts to Combat Speed-up and to Preserve Health Regarding Women's Conference, May 15, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 317)
- Facts for Political Action, May 15, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 318)
- The Truth about the Fifth Amendment, June 1954 (Box 5, Folder 318)
- Stop the Runaways Regarding Runaway Shops, June 1954 (Box 5, Folder 319)
- The Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, June 1954 (Box 5, Folder 319)
- The Miserable Record of the 83rd Congress, September 1954 (Box 5, Folder 319)
- They Represent You Regarding New York City League of Women Voters, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 319)
- This Is the Proof Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry and General Electric, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 319)
- Brownell's Answer to Unemployment Regarding Red-baiting and Brownell Butler Bill, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 320)
- Defeat Anti-labor Politicians in '54, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 320)
- GE Violates U.S. Constitution Regarding Red-baiting, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 320)
- The Emspak Case Regarding Red-baiting, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 320)
- Together We Shall Go Forward Regarding Schenectady General Electric, Women and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 320)
- GE Calls on Un-Americans Again, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 321)
- Big Business Wants Union-Busting Laws Regarding Red-baiting, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 321)
- The Technique of McCarthyism in the Labor Movement, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 321)
- The Informer Regarding Red-baiting, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 321)
- Unfair Regarding American Safety Razor Boycotts and Runaway Shop, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 321)
- People Warned on Last Minute Freedom Attack Regarding Red-baiting, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 322)
- Tooling Up for Mass Repression Regarding Red-baiting, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 322)
- FE-UE Exposes UAW's Share the Misery Plan for Harvester Workers, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 322)
- 2nd National Converence on Problems of Working Women, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 322)
- Conference to Repeal the Walter-McCarran Law, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 322)
- Call to a People's Conference in Washington, D.C. to Repeal the McCarran Act, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 322)
- Job Discrimination Breeds Depression Regarding Racism, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 323)
- UE Guide to Fair Practices, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 324)
- Subversive, 1954 Regarding Red-baiting and Communist Control Act (Box 5, Folder 324)
- A Message to All GE Schenectady Workers from UE 301 Regarding IUE Interunion Rivalry, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 324)
- Call to a Philadelphia Area Conference to Repeal the Walter-McCarran Law, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 324)
- Honest FE-Unionism or UAW-CIO Sell-Out, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 324)
- Cartoon Calendar, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 325)
- A Dog-tag for Labor Regarding Red-baiting, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 326)
- Defeat Anti-Labor Politicians, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 327)
- A Book You Will Never Forget Regarding Mill Town, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 327)
- If You are Laid Off Regarding Unemployment, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 327)
- The Truth About the 5th Amendment, January 1955 (Box 5, Folder 328)
- Sister UE Goes to Washington Regarding 3rd National Women's Conference, March 1955 (Box 5, Folder 328)
- Security for Them Regarding Racism, May 1955 (Box 5, Folder 328)
- Radio Fact Sheet Regarding Radio Broadcasts, September 14, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 329)
- The Matles Case Regarding Red-baiting, October 1955 (Box 5, Folder 329)
- Matles Case Manual Regarding Red-baiting, October 1955 (Box 5, Folder 330)
- The Westinghouse Strike, November 1955 (Box 5, Folder 331)
- The W 5-Year Package Regarding Westinghouse Strikes, November 1955 (Box 5, Folder 331)
- Democracy v. Force and Violence Regardign Segregation, December 1955 (Box 5, Folder 331)
- 1955 Cartoon Calendar (Box 5, Folder 332)
- Dedicated to UE-ASR Workers Regarding Runaway Shops, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 333)
- UE Collective Bargaining and Legislative Program, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 334)
- UE Collective Bargaining and Legislative Program for [1955] (Box 5, Folder 335)
- IUE Exposes Own Fraud Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 336)
- Shall They Sit in Judgement on the Bill of Rights? Regarding Red-baiting and Gojack Case, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 336)
- 4th National Conference on the Problems of Working Women, March 1956 (Box 5, Folder 337)
- Support Locked Out UE Westinghouse Workers at Essington Pennsylvania, April 1956 (Box 5, Folder 337)
- Program, National Womens Conference, May 19, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 337)
- Democratic Unionism-Worth Fighting For Regarding Labor Unity and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, May 1956 (Box 5, Folder 337)
- Tips on Radio Regarding League of Women Voters, July 1956 (Box 5, Folder 338)
- The Pittsburgh Case Regarding Smith Act and Red-baiting, September 1956 (Box 5, Folder 338)
- First Taft-Hartley Victim Regarding Red-baiting and Hupman Case, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 338)
- The Fund for the Republic, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 338)
- American Civil Liberties Union Statement Regarding Censorship, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 338)
- Facts for Voters Regarding New York League of Women Voters, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 338)
- Speed-up and Health Regarding Women's Conference, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 339)
- UE Fair Practices Regarding Segregation, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 340)
- Summary, Women's Conference, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 341)
- Liberty Regarding American Civil Liberties Union Report, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 342)
- Women in the 1956 Elections Regarding Women's Conference and Segregation (Box 5, Folder 343)
- United Labor Can Win Economic Equality for Women Regarding Women's Conference, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 344)
- UE Twentieth Anniversary Calendar, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 345)
- The New York State Security Risk Law Regarding Red-baiting, January 1957 (Box 5, Folder 346)
- Brownell-Eastland-McCarthy vs. Matles Regarding Red-baiting, January 1957 (Box 5, Folder 346)
- GEB Statement on Federal Aid to Education Regarding Segregation, March 21, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 347)
- The Same Paid Witnesses Who Lied About Matles Also Fingered Carey, April 1957 (Box 5, Folder 347)
- Facts for Voters Regarding League of Women Voters, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 347)
- Presenting the International League for the Rights of Man, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 347)
- The Proud Record of UE in Sylvania, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 347)
- The Union With A Difference You Can Feel, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 347)
- The New York Civil Liberties Union, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 347)
- Cartoon Calendar, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 348)
- UE Sample Contract, October 1958 (Box 5, Folder 349)
- UE Sample Contract, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 350)
- UE Says Stop the Depression Now Regarding Unemployment, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 351)
- IAM-AFLCIO Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 351)
- From Official United States Government Documents Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 351)
- IUE Defeats, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 352)
- Here's How It Works Regarding Inter-union Rivalry: IUE Inter-union Rivalry, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 352)
- UE 1958 Collective Bargaining Program (Box 5, Folder 352)
- The Question of Bomb Tests Regarding Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 352)
- Justice-In Your Hands Regarding League of Women Voters, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 352)
- Unemployment Regarding Automation, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 352)
- Here Is the Proof Regarding Red-baiting, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 352)
- UE Cartoon Calendar, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 353)
- George Leader Regarding Political Action, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 353)
- From Official United States Government Documents Regarding Red-baiting, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 353)
- UE Minimum Contract Requirements, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 354)
- Getting Out the News Regarding Publicity, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 355)
- Increasing Unemployment and the Need for the Shorter Work Week, January 31, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 356)
- Who Said It Regarding Hours and Unemployment, February 1959 (Box 5, Folder 356)
- The Union With a Difference You Can Feel, Fourth Printing Regarding Organization, March 1959 (Box 5, Folder 357)
- For the General Welfare Regarding UE Programs, November 1959 (Box 5, Folder 358)
- A New Approach Regarding Negotiations and Shorter Work Week, December 1959 (Box 5, Folder 359)
- Elmira GE Back in UE Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 359)
- 5 Ways to Make Sure of Your Job Regarding Hours, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 359)
- Unemployment Regarding Automation, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 360)
- They Said It Couldn't Be Done, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 360)
- The Union With A Difference You Can Feel, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 361)
- UE Cartoon Calendar, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 362)
- Time to Come Back Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, February 1960 (Box 5, Folder 363)
- UE and Government Work Regarding Military Contracts and Inter-union Rivalry, March 1960 (Box 5, Folder 364)
- Time to Come Back Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, June 1960 (Box 5, Folder 365)
- The Inflation Racketeers, July 1960 (Box 5, Folder 366)
- That's A Pretty Lively Corpse, Pal Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, July 1960 (Box 5, Folder 367)
- What Price IUE Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, October 1960 (Box 5, Folder 367)
- Schenectady Needs a Union Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry and Schenectady General Electric, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 367)
- One Good Union Regarding General Electric and Westinghouse Inter-union Rivalry, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 367)
- UE News Special Edition, April 1960 (Box 5, Folder 367)
- Stop the Seniority Sell-Out Regarding General Electric and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 368)
- I'm Voting UE Regarding Lynn General Electric and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 368)
- Polaris Missile Job Assigned to Erie GE Works Regarding Lynn General Electric and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 368)
- UE Local 201 Program and Policy Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 368)
- You Can Win, Too Regarding Organization and New Haven, January 1961 (Box 5, Folder 369)
- The Aircraft Strike Regarding United Auto Workers and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, April 1961 (Box 5, Folder 369)
- Sing Out, December 1961 (Box 5, Folder 370)
- UE President Asks Congress to Speed Pay for Jobless, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 370)
- The Illusion of Civil Defense, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 371)
- The Local Publicity Committee, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 371)
- The Myth, the Money, the Many Regarding Inflation, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 372)
- National Conference on Problems of Working Women, January 13, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 373)
- 25 Years of UE Gains in GE, February 1962 (Box 5, Folder 373)
- 25 Years of UE Gains in GE, April 1962 (Box 5, Folder 374)
- 25 Years of UE Gains in GE, May 1962 (Box 5, Folder 375)
- 25 Years of UE Gains in Westinghouse, June 1962 (Box 5, Folder 376)
- What's Behind It? Regarding IUE Factionalism, November 1962 (Box 5, Folder 376)
- Facts for Collective Bargaining at General Electric and Westinghouse, November 10, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 377)
- Welcome to Allen-Bradley Regarding Local 1111 and Membership Drive, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 377)
- Facts for GE and W Workers, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 378)
- 1962 Calendar (Box 5, Folder 379)
- Report on Civil Rights, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 380)
- Join UE Local 1111 Now, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 380)
- UE Employees Pension Plan, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 380)
- Your Right to Join UE Is Guaranteed by Law Regarding Organization, April 19, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 381)
- La Ley Asegura el Derecho de Ingresar a UE Regarding Organization, April 1963 (Box 5, Folder 381)
- JFK to IUE Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, April 1963 (Box 5, Folder 381)
- A Record of UE Gains Regarding Organization, May 1963 (Box 5, Folder 382)
- Esta es Historia UE y sus Ganancias Regarding Organization, May 1963 (Box 5, Folder 382)
- UE Leaders See Things Your Way Regarding Inter-union Rivalry and Organization, June 1966 (Box 5, Folder 382)
- Los Dirigentes de UE, Ven, Piensen y Sienten Igual Que Usted Regarding Organization and Inter-union Rivalry, June 1963 (Box 5, Folder 382)
- Could You Call This A Great Union Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, September 1963 (Box 5, Folder 383)
- UE Shop Steward Guide, October 1963 (Box 5, Folder 384)
- The People Must Act to Heal America's Wounds Regarding Political Action, December 1963 (Box 5, Folder 385)
- The 1963 UE Settlement with GE, December 1963 (Box 5, Folder 385)
- The 1963 UE Settlement with Westinghouse, December 1963 (Box 5, Folder 385)
- New Perspectives on American Security, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 385)
- Men and Machines Regarding ILWU, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 386)
- UE 1963 Cartoon Calendar (Box 6, Folder 387)
- IUE Vice-president Resigns Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 388)
- A Quarter Century of Un-Americana Regarding House Un-American Activities Committee, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 388)
- How to Improve Your Figure Without Going on a Diet, January 1964 (Box 6, Folder 389)
- Together We Win Regarding Women, July 1964 (Box 6, Folder 389)
- Barry Goldwater Regarding Political Action, September 1964 (Box 6, Folder 390)
- Goldwaterism Regarding Political Action, September 1964 (Box 6, Folder 390)
- The Settlement in Auto, December 2, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 390)
- Civil Rights Act of 1964 (Box 6, Folder 391)
- You Can Win Too Regarding Organization and New Haven, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 392)
- Cartoon Calendar, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 392)
- What Should Union Officials Be Paid, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 392)
- Report on IUE Convention, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 393)
- Why Was Industry For Johnson? Regarding Political Action, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 393)
- Report on IUE Convention, Large Edition, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 394)
- Report on IUE Convention, Large Edition, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 395)
- Don't Let Them Water Down Medicare, January 1965 (Box 6, Folder 396)
- We Propose One Union for Electrical Workers, February 1965 (Box 6, Folder 396)
- The Union with a Difference You Can Feel, February 1965 (Box 6, Folder 396)
- The Proud Record of An American Union Regarding Organization, February 1965 (Box 6, Folder 397)
- Words into Action Regarding Blacks, July 1965 (Box 6, Folder 398)
- The Mississippi Challenge Regarding Mississippi Freedom Democratic Party, August 10, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 399)
- Read UE's Answer to GE Regarding Negotiations, General Electric and Pensions, August 1965 (Box 6, Folder 400)